in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can create this simple badge style
您可以创建这个简单的徽章样式
logo using inkscape so I'll come over
使用Inkscape的徽标，所以我会过来
here into a new document and get started
在此处转换为新文档并开始使用
the first thing we want to do is change
我们想做的第一件事就是改变
the size of the canvas so that it is a
画布的大小，因此它是
square so I'm going to open up document
正方形所以我要打开文档
Properties by pressing control shift and
通过按Ctrl Shift和
D on the keyboard if you're a Mac User
如果您是Mac用户，请按键盘上的D键
that would be command shift d and I want
那就是指挥班次d，我要
to change the width and the height so
要将宽度和高度更改为
that they're equal so for my example
他们是平等的，对我来说就是这样
here I will use 800 by 800 and then I
在这里我将使用800乘以800，然后我
will close out of that and then I want
会结束这一切然后我想
to zoom into 100 % so I'm going to press
放大100%，所以我要按下
one on the keyboard to zoom into 100%
键盘上的一个按钮可放大到100%
and now I'm going to create a circle to
现在我要创建一个圆圈来
place in the middle of the canvas here
放在画布中间的位置
which we will wrap the text around so
我们将对其进行换行，以便
I'm going to grab the circles and
我要抓起圆圈
ellipses tool I'll click and drag to
我要单击并拖动到的椭圆工具
create a circle I'm going to hold the
创建一个圆圈，我要拿着
control key while I do that so it's nice
当我这样做的时候按下Ctrl键，这样很好
and perfectly round and I'll make it
完美的圆润，我会做到的
about that big relative to the size of
大约那么大，相对于大小
the canvas and I want to convert this to
画布和我想把这个转换成
a path so I'll come up here to where it
一条小路，所以我会走到这里
says object and I will go to no I'm
说反对，我会说不，我是
sorry I'll go to path and I will select
对不起，我会去路径，我会选择
object to path and then I want to send
对象到路径，然后我想要发送
Center this directly on the canvas so I
把这个直接放在画布上，这样我
will open up the aligned distribute menu
将打开对齐的分发菜单
by going to object and selecting aligned
通过转到对象并选择对齐
distribute and from this drop down over
从这个下拉列表中分配到
here I want to choose page and now that
我想在这里选择页面，而现在
we are aligning this relative to the
我们正在将此与
page I want to align this on the
我想把这个放在
vertical and the horizontal axis we're
纵轴和横轴我们是
selecting the center options there and
在那里选择中心选项，然后
now it's perfectly uh centered on the
现在它完全，呃，集中在
canvas like that so now I'm going to
像这样的画布，所以现在我要
create some text to put on the circle
创建一些文本放在圆圈上
let me grab my selection tool first I'm
让我先拿起我的选择工具
gon to adjust the size of this a little
Gon要稍微调整一下这个的大小
bit I'm going to hold control and shift
我要按住控制键和变速键
and scale this down a little bit because
稍微缩小一下规模，因为
the text is going to be placed up here
文本将被放在这里
and then down here as well so I want to
然后在这里，所以我想
leave some room around the edges of the
在边缘周围留出一些空间
canvas so that I have enough room for
画布，这样我就有足够的空间
that and now I'm going to create the
现在我要创建
text to be placed on the circle here so
文本要放在此处的圆圈上，因此
I'll grab the text tool which is located
我去拿定位的文本工具
over here and I will click on the canvas
在这里，我将点击画布
to create some text I'm going to write
为了创建一些文本，我将写下
for this demonstration I'm just going to
在这个演示中，我只想
write inkscape for the top line of text
将Inkscape写在文本的最上面一行
we're going to create two different text
我们将创建两个不同的文本
items one for the top line that goes
第一项是顶线的
along the top of the circle and another
沿着圆圈的顶部和另一个圆圈
text item that goes along the bottom so
位于底部的文本项，因此
I'm going to write inkscape here I'm
我要写Inkscape在这里我是
going to change this font to something
要将此字体更改为
else I'm going to go to text and select
否则，我将转到文本并选择
text and font and from this editor I
文本和字体，并且从该编辑器中我
will choose a different font to work
将选择不同的字体来工作
with you can work whatever work with
有了你，你可以做任何事情
whatever font you'd like for this uh
您想要什么字体呢？
design I like the monserat font uh which
设计我喜欢Monserat字体
is a free font if you want to download
是一种免费字体，如果您想下载
and install that otherwise you can use
并安装它，否则您可以使用
whatever font you'd like and now I want
任何你喜欢的字体，现在我想要
to put some spacing between these
为了在它们之间留出一些间距
letters so let me come up here to where
字母，所以让我到这里来
it says spacing
上面写着间隔
and I want to add this I want to add
我想加上这一点，我想加上
like three to this value I'll try I'll
像这个值的三倍，我会试一下，我会的
start off with three and then we'll take
从三个开始，然后我们就
it from there and we want to make sure
从那里，我们想确保
that this text is centered so come over
这篇文章居中，所以过来一下
here to the alignment option and Center
此处为对齐选项和居中
it like that now it's not going to
它就是这样，现在它不会
visibly change but it's important for
明显的改变，但这对
what we're going to do next placing it
我们下一步要做的是放置它
on the circle so let me grab my
所以让我拿起我的
selection tool now I'm just going to
选择工具，现在我要去
bring the text over here to the circle
把课文放到圆圈里
and just try to eyeball the size of it
试着看看它的大小
as it is right now it's going to be
就像现在一样，它将是
wrapped around the top side of this
缠绕在这个的顶端
circle so you may want to make it a
圈起来，这样你可能会想把它变成
little bigger or smaller depending on
更大或更小，取决于
the size of your circle and I'm holding
你的圈子有多大，我拿着
in control and shift while I scale like
当我像这样伸缩时，控制和转换
this so it scales it evenly from the
这样，它就可以从
center and I'll make my text about that
居中，我会把我的文字写成这个
big and now I will duplicate this I will
很大，现在我要复制这个我会的
right click it and go to
右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate and I will make this one I'll
复制品，我会做这个，我会
make this one the bottom line of text
将这一行设置为文本的底行
that I want down here so let me go back
我想来这里，所以让我回去吧
to my text tool and I will change this
添加到我的文本工具，我将更改此设置
one to logo
One to徽标
design and now what we can do is let me
现在我们能做的就是让我
adjust this the spacing between this one
调整这个和这个之间的间距
let me just make sure that's equal okay
让我来确认一下，好吗？
this one's a little larger I'm going to
这个稍微大一点，我要去
adjust this I want to make sure that's
调整这个，我想确保这是
even for both of these I want both of
即使这两个我都想要。
these to be the same amount of
这些都是相同数量的
spacing there we
我们在那里有空位
go and now I'm going to take this text
去吧，现在我要把这篇课文
item right here I'm going to select it
就在这里，我要选择它
hold shift select the circle and with
按住Shift键选择圆，然后使用
them both selected go to text and select
这两个选项都被选中，转到文本并选择
put on path and now click off of it to
放在PATH上，然后单击它以
deselect everything and then click on
取消选择所有内容，然后单击
just the circle click on it again to get
只需再次点击圆圈即可获得
the rotation handles and then hold your
旋转手柄，然后按住您的
control key and grab the rotation handle
Ctrl键并抓住旋转手柄
in the corner then there and rotate it
在角落里，然后在那里旋转它
around until the text is upright like
直到文本竖直，就像
that and now I'm going to change the
现在我要改变
color of this so let me make this a
这个的颜色，所以让我把它变成
lighter shade of gray something like
浅一点的灰色，有点像
that so I just so I can see the text a
这样我就可以看到文本a
little better up against the uh the
更好的对抗，呃，
canvas there and what I'll do now is I'm
画布在那里，我现在要做的是
going to create another Circle for the
要创建另一个圆
bottom line of text so let me deselect
文本的最后一行，所以让我取消选择
that by clicking off of it let me move
通过点击它，让我移动
this out of the way I'm going to create
这不是我要创建的方式
another another Circle let me grab my
另一个圆圈让我抓住我的
circles and ellipses tool click and drag
圆和椭圆工具单击并拖动
to create a circle hold the control key
要创建圆，请按住Ctrl键
and I want this circle to be bigger so
我希望这个圈子更大，所以
I'll make this one bigger and I'll make
我会把这个做大，我会做
this one A different shade that from the
这个颜色和那个不一样
other Circle I'll make this one maybe a
另一个圈子我会把这个弄成一个
darker gray and then I'll take this one
深灰色的，然后我就买这件了。
I want to lower this to the bottom so
我想把这个降到最低，这样
I'll click this button right here that
我会点击这里的这个按钮，
says lower to the bottom and I'm going
说低到最低，我要去
to Center this on the page as well so
使其在页面上居中显示，以便
let me come back over here to my
让我回到我的
alignment menu and I will Center this
对齐菜单和我将此居中
vertically and horizontally and now I'm
垂直和水平，现在我是
going to scale down this circle I'm
我要缩小这个圈子的规模
going to grab this Arrow right here and
抓住这个箭头，就在这里
hold control and shift and scale it down
按住Ctrl键、Shift键并按比例缩小
until the top of the circle touches the
直到圆圈的顶部接触到
top of that line of text right there and
就在那行文字的顶端
now I'm going to convert this to a path
现在，我将把它转换成一条路径
by going to path and selecting object to
通过转到路径并选择对象到
path and now I'm going to grab my text
路径，现在我要抓起我的文本
item right here and I'll do the same
就在这里，我也会这么做的
thing that I did previously I'm going to
我之前做过的事情，我要去
hold shift I'm going to click on the
按住Shift键我要单击
larger Circle this time and go to text
这次转到大圆圈并转到文本
and SE select put on
和SE选择穿上
path click off of it to deselect select
路径单击它以取消选择选择
just the large Circle click on it again
只是大圆圈再次点击它
to get the rotation handles and rotate
获取旋转控制柄并旋转
this around while holding control until
在按住Ctrl直到
it's
它是
upright and now we just want to flip the
直立，现在我们只想翻转
circle so I'm going to come over here to
所以我要到这里来
where it says flip vertical and click on
上面写着垂直翻转并点击
that and now we have the text down there
现在我们有了下面的文本
like that so what we can do at this
就像这样，我们现在能做的就是
point is we can adjust the circles to
重点是我们可以将圆圈调整到
make sure that this text fills up as
确保此文本填充为
much area as we want it to fill up so if
我们希望它填满的区域很大，所以如果
you notice right now there's a lot of
你注意到现在有很多
empty space on this side of the circle
圆圈这边的空白处
on both sides between the two text items
在两个文本项之间的两侧
let's say you want to close that in a
假设您想要在一个
bit I'm going to select both circles you
我要把你的两个圆圈都选中
can do that by holding shift and
可以通过按住Shift键和
clicking on each and then I'm going to
点击每个按钮，然后我将
hold control and shift and scale them
按住Ctrl和Shift并对其进行缩放
down like like this and if you notice
像这样向下，如果你注意到
you can decrease the space between the
您可以减小
words or you can increase the space
文字，或者你可以增加空间
between the words whatever works best
在这两个词之间，最有效的
for your uh however you have things
对于你，呃，不管你有什么东西
arranged right now I want to leave some
现在就安排好了，我想留下一些。
space in there because we're going to
那里的空间，因为我们要
put we're going to be putting these uh
我们要把这些放在
these little tails on the end here so
这里末端的这些小尾巴，所以
I'm going to leave a little bit of space
我要留一点空间
for that and I'm going to leave that
为了这一点，我要把它
just as it is and now I'm just going to
就像现在我要做的就是
adjust my circles to make up for the uh
调整我的圈子来弥补呃
Missing space there because if you
缺少空格是因为如果您
notice this is uh the larger Circle here
注意这是，呃，这里是更大的圆圈
is no longer aligned with the other text
不再与其他文本对齐
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and that looks a little better and I'm
这看起来好一点了，我
going to increase the spacing between
要增加之间的间距
these letters down here because these
这里的这些字母是因为这些
letters look a little closer together
字母看起来更近了一点
than these ones do just because of the
而不是这些人，仅仅是因为
Contour of the circle that's just how it
圆圈的轮廓就是这样
works so let me grab my text tool let me
所以让我抓起我的文本工具让我
select all of the text I'll come over
选择我要过来的所有文本
here to my spacing and I'll put a little
在这里到我的间距，我会放一点
more spacing in there maybe for this one
这里有更多的空间，也许是为了这个
I'll try five and that looks a lot
我要试五个，看起来很多。
better so what we're going to do now
所以我们现在要做的是
once you're happy with your text and the
一旦你对你的文本和
placing and the spacing between
放置位置和间距
everything Click on each of these
所有内容都点击其中的每一个
circles and let's turn off the fill
圈起来，让我们关掉填充物
color Al together so select it and then
将铝涂在一起，选择它，然后
come over here to this red X and click
来到这里，点击这个红色的X
on that and I'll do the same thing I'll
我也会做同样的事
come over here to this circle and click
到这里来这个圆圈，点击
on the Red X over here now from this
从现在开始在这里的红色X上
point forward it's important to remember
向前看，记住这一点很重要
that this these text items are linked to
这些文本项链接到
the invisible circles that they're
他们是看不见的圆圈
placed on so try not to click or drag
放置在上面，所以尽量不要点击或拖动
any of these text items out of the way
这些文本项目中的任何一个都不会挡道
otherwise you're going to mess up the
否则你会搞砸
balance of everything and if at any
一切的平衡，如果有的话
point you need to go back to those
你需要回到那些点上
circles and adjust things if you notice
如果你注意到了，就圈起来，调整一下
you can't click on those circles now
你现在不能点击那些圆圈
because they're invisible you can get to
因为它们是隐形的，你可以
them by going to view and going to
通过查看和查看它们
display mode and selecting outline and
显示模式和选择轮廓和
once you can see the outlines then you
一旦你能看到轮廓，你就可以
can click on them and select them that's
可以点击并选择它们，即
just in case you need to go back and
以防万一你需要回去
edit this at all though so I'm happy
尽管如此，还是编辑一下吧，我很高兴
with how it is so I'm going to go back
所以我要回到过去
to my regular display mode I'll go to
到我的常规显示模式，我将转到
view I'll go to display mode and select
查看我将进入显示模式并选择
normal and now I'm going to create these
很正常，现在我要创建这些
Rings going around either side of the
环围绕着地球的两边
text here so let me come back in here
在这里发短信，让我回到这里
I'm going to go back to my circles and
我要回到我的圈子里去
ellipses
省略号
tool click and drag to create a circle
工具单击并拖动以创建圆
ircle I'm going to hold control so we
我要控制局面，所以我们
have a perfectly round circle and I want
做一个完美的圆圈，我想要
to get rid of the fill color and I want
去掉填充颜色，我想
to add a black stroke so I'm going to
添加一个黑色笔划，所以我要
hold shift and click on the black color
按住Shift键并单击黑色
over here and then I will grab my
在这里，然后我会拿起我的
selection tool and I will Center this on
选择工具和我将以此为中心
the page as well and now I just want to
页面也是如此，现在我只想
scale this down so that it encompasses
缩小规模，使其包含以下内容
the text there like that and what I'm
那里的文字是这样的，我是什么
going to do now is I'm going to come up
现在要做的就是我要上来
here to this option where it says when
在这里到这个选项，它说什么时候
scaling objects scale the stroke width
缩放对象缩放笔触宽度
by the same proportion make sure you
以同样的比例确保你
have that deselected if you have it in
如果已选中，请取消选中该选项
right now go ahead and disable that and
现在，继续禁用它，然后
now I'll come over here to my well
现在我要到我的井里来
actually I want to open the fill and
事实上，我想打开填充物
stroke menu so I'll come up here to
中风菜单，所以我会来这里
where it says object and go to fill in
在那里它显示对象，然后去填写
stroke and I want to click on the stroke
笔划，我想点击笔划
style Tab and I want to change the size
Style Tab和我要更改大小
or the weight of this stroke so that
或者这一划的重量，所以
it's kind of consistent with the text
这与课文内容有些一致
there it already looks like a pretty
在那里，它已经看起来像一个漂亮的
good size as it is but maybe a little
它的尺寸很好，但可能有一点
smaller it would look better so I'm
小一点会更好看，所以我
going to try eight and see how that
我要试试8个，看看这个结果
looks maybe
看起来可能是
nine okay nine looks good so I'll leave
9点，好的，9点看起来不错，所以我要走了。
that as it is and now I'm going to right
事实就是如此，现在我要做正确的事
click this and go to duplicate and then
单击此选项并转到复制，然后
I'll hold control and shift and scale
我会保持控制，换挡和缩放
this down so that we have this ring on
把这个放下，这样我们就可以戴上这个戒指了
the inside here and if you notice as I
这里的内部，如果你像我一样注意到
scale this down the stroke weight stays
按比例缩小笔划重量停留
the same size that's why we disabled
同样的大小这就是为什么我们禁用了
that option up there so let me make this
上面的选项，所以让我来做这个
a little bigger what I'm looking at here
更大一点，我现在看到的是
is the spacing between the bottom and
是底部和底部之间的间距
the top here we want to make sure
这里的顶部我们想要确保
there's about an equal amount of padding
有大约等量的填充物
between each of between each of those
在其中的每一个之间
there we go that looks pretty good let
我们走吧，看起来很不错，让我们
me zoom out and now what I'm going to do
我缩小了，现在我要做的是
is I'm going to create this little uh
我要创造这个小小的呃
this little side ring that you see going
你看到的这个小小的侧环
along the side here so let me zoom out
沿着这一边，所以让我把它放大
let me come back over here and I'm going
让我回到这里，我要走了
to duplicate this again I'm going to
为了再复制一次，我要
right click it and go to duplicate and
右键单击它，然后转到复制和
hold control and shift and scale this
按住Ctrl键、Shift键并进行缩放
down so that it's going about halfway
向下，所以它大约在半路上
through these other two rings right here
穿过另外两个环，就在这里
and that's looking good okay so now I
这看起来不错，好的，所以现在我
just want to keep these portions of the
我只想保留这一部分
Ring I want to clip off the parts where
戒指我想剪掉下面的部分
they're going through the text so let me
他们正在看课文，所以让我来
grab my rectangle tool and let me click
抓起我的矩形工具，让我点击
and drag to draw a rectangle going
并拖动以绘制一个矩形
through the area of that ring that I'd
穿过那个戒指的区域，我会
like to keep let me change the color of
喜欢保持让我改变颜色的
this let me bring down its opacity so I
这让我降低了它的不透明度，所以我
can see through it and I'll come over
我能看穿它，我就过去
here to my selection tool and I'm just
这是我的选择工具，我只是
going to adjust this if you notice the
如果您注意到
top of the rectangle is going right here
矩形的顶部位于此处
where that text begins and I want the
文本开始的地方，我想要
same thing down here about the same
这里也是一样的，差不多的
about the same
伯仲之间
amount and once you do that you can hold
数量，一旦你这样做了，你就可以持有
shift and click on the ring so you have
按住Shift键并单击该环，这样您就可以
both the ring and the rectangle selected
环和矩形都被选中
and go to path and select
并转到路径并选择
cut path and then click off of it to
剪切路径，然后将其关闭以
deselect everything and now you could
取消选择所有内容，现在您可以
take the top half of this ring press
拿着这台环压机的上半部分
delete to get rid of it and the same
删除以摆脱它和相同的
thing down here click on that press
这里的东西点击那个印刷机
delete to get rid of it and if you
删除以清除它，并且如果您
notice my Strokes right here have
请注意，我的笔划在这里
rounded caps on the end of them if yours
如果是你的，在它们的末端有圆帽
are squared and you want to make them
是平方的，而你想让它们
rounded like mine just come over here
像我一样圆圆的就到这里来
into the stroke style Tab and you can
添加到笔划样式选项卡中，您可以
see the cap setting by default is set to
请参见默认情况下将上限设置设置为
rounded if I make it Square we get that
四舍五入，如果我把它变成方形，我们就会得到
effect right there but I like how it
效果就在那里，但我喜欢它的样子
looks better rounded so I'm going to put
四舍五入看起来更好所以我要把
that back to
又回到了
rounded and now we're going to create
四舍五入，现在我们要创建
these little ribbons on the end here or
这里末端的这些小丝带或者
these little Tails whatever you want to
这些小尾巴，随便你想要什么
call them so let me come back in here
打电话给他们，让我回到这里
and try to remember what this value is
并尝试记住这个值是什么
the size of your stroke the size of the
笔划的大小等于
stroke should be the same for the entire
笔划应与整个笔划相同
design so I'm working with a nine pixel
设计，所以我使用9个像素
stroke for my design so I want to make
为我的设计画了笔，所以我想
sure that everything that I create from
确保我所创造的一切
here on out also has a nine pixel stroke
这里On Out也有9个像素的笔划
so let me grab my rectangle tool I'm
所以让我拿起我的矩形工具
going to click and drag over this area
要在此区域上单击并拖动
of the circle where I want that Banner
我想要的横幅所在的圆圈
to
至
be and I'm going to convert this to a
BE，我将把它转换为
path I will go to path and select object
路径I将转到路径并选择对象
to
至
path I'll grab my selection tool I'll
我会拿起我的选择工具我会
come back over here to my alignment menu
回到这里到我的校准菜单
and I want to make sure that this is
我想要确保这是
aligned vertically and horizontally as
垂直和水平对齐为
well and I'll make this one maybe a
好的，我会把这件事做成一个
little
一点儿
smaller there we go let me adjust the
小一点，我们走，让我调整一下
alignment I'm going to remove the fill
对齐我要移除填充物
color I'm going to hold shift and click
颜色我要按住Shift键并单击
on the color black to add that stroke on
在黑色上添加笔触
there and again I want this stroke to be
我一次又一次地想要这一次中风
the same weight as the other Strokes I
与其他笔划相同的权重为
can already tell that this is larger so
已经可以看出这个更大了
let me come back over here to my fill
让我回到这里尽情享受吧
and stroke menu and I'm going to change
和中风菜单，我要改变
this back to
这回到了
nine and now we're going to put little
九个，现在我们要把一些
indents on the ends here so let me grab
两端有凹痕，让我拿一下
my nodes tool I'll click and drag over
我的节点工具，我将单击并拖动到其上
these two nodes and I'll click this
这两个节点，我会点击这个
button up here that says insert new
这里有一个按钮，上面写着插入新的
nodes into selected
将节点添加到选定对象
segments and that's going to put a new
细分市场，这将使一个新的
node in there and I'll do the same thing
节点在那里，我会做同样的事情
over here I'll select these two and I
在这里，我会选择这两个，然后我
will add a new node in there and now I
将在其中添加一个新节点，现在我
just want to click and drag over those
我只想在上面点击并拖动
two middle nodes that I just have those
两个中间节点，我只有那些
two Center nodes selected and I will
选择了两个中心节点，我将
enable this option up here in the tool
在工具的此处启用此选项
settings menu that says show
显示显示的设置菜单
transformation handles for selected
所选对象的变换句柄
nodes and when I click on that you can
节点，当我点击该节点时，您可以
see we now have these transformation
看，我们现在有了这些转变
handles I'm going to click and drag on
我要单击并拖动的控制柄
this Arrow I'm going to hold control and
这个箭头我要控制和控制
shift and scale this in like that so
像这样移动和缩放它
that it scales from both sides and we
它从两边扩展，我们
end up with that sort of effect right
最终会有这样的效果，对吧
there and now I will disable this
现在，我将禁用此功能
setting and go back to my selection
设置并返回到我的选择
tool and I'm just going to adjust the
工具，我只是要调整
height of this I'm going to make this a
最重要的是，我要把这件事
little smaller height-wise because I
身高要小一点，因为我
notice not much of this part of the
注意不多的这一部分
design is sticking out there and I'd
设计是突出的，我会
like to see more of that so I'm going to
我想看更多这样的节目，所以我要
adjust this height accordingly and I
相应地调整此高度，我
will Center that and now we just got to
威尔把它放在中心，现在我们只需要
clip out these areas from here if you
从这里剪掉这些区域，如果你
notice we removed all of these unwanted
请注意，我们删除了所有不需要的
areas so let's go back and do all of
所以让我们回到过去，做所有
that uh what I'm going to do is first
我要做的是首先
I'm going to select I'm going to select
我要选择我要选择
these the smaller ring in the center in
这是中间较小的环
the center here I will right click that
中间这个，我会右击那个
and go to duplicate and then hold shift
然后转到复制，然后按住Shift
and click on that rectangle and go to
然后单击该矩形并转到
path and
路径和
select cut
选择切割
path and now we can click off of it to
路径，现在我们可以单击它以
deselect and we can just get rid of
取消选择，我们就可以删除
these pieces on the inside here and now
这些碎片就在里面，此时此地
I'm going to come over here I'm going to
我要过来，我要去
select this object right click go to
选择此对象，右键单击转到
duplicate hold shift click on this path
重复按住Shift键并单击此路径
right here and go to path and select cut
就在这里，然后转到路径并选择剪切
path and then I can get rid of
然后我就可以摆脱
that and then one more time I will do
然后我会再做一次
the same thing to the larger ring now so
现在更大的环也是一样的
I'll take this object right click it go
我要拿着这个物体，右键点击，开始
to duplicate
复制
hold shift click on the larger ring go
按住Shift键，点击较大的环上的GO
to path and select cut path and now I
到路径并选择剪切路径，现在我
can get rid of this as well now if you
现在也可以摆脱这个，如果你
notice over here this stroke is sticking
注意这里，这个笔划卡住了。
out you could barely see it but there's
在外面，你几乎看不到它，但有
a tiny little bump sticking out there uh
一个小小的凸起伸在外面，嗯
you can adjust that by grabbing your
你可以通过抓起你的
nodes tool and selecting it and then
Nodes工具并将其选中，然后
just moving it over a little bit I'm
只是把它移过去一点，我正在
going to hold control while I do that to
当我这样做的时候，我会控制
make sure it does not leave the
确保它不会离开
horizontal axis and then I'll just move
水平轴，然后我就会移动
it in a little bit there we go that
再过一会儿，我们就可以开始了
looks better and I'll do the same thing
看起来好多了，我也会做同样的事
over here I'll click on this node and
在这里，我将单击此节点，然后
then just hold control and move that in
然后只需保持控制并将其移动到
like that and now I'm going to repeat
像这样，现在我要重复一遍
this process over here on this side so
这个过程在这边，所以
let me go back to my selection tool make
让我回到我的选择工具Make
a duplicate of this one instead of right
这件的复制品，而不是对的
clicking and going to duplicate you can
点击并复制您可以
just press contrl D on your keyboard or
只需按键盘上的Ctrl D键或
command D if you're using Mac to
如果您正在使用Mac执行以下操作，请按D键
duplicate it hold shift click on this
复制它，按住Shift键，单击此按钮
stroke go to path and select cut path
笔划转到路径并选择剪切路径
get rid of that piece right there and I
把那块扔了，我就可以
will do the same thing one more time I'm
我会再做一次同样的事情
going to duplicate that hold shift click
要复制按住Shift键单击
on the circle and we will cut the path
在圆圈上，我们将开辟一条道路
and get rid of that and there we go so
把它扔掉，我们就走吧
now I'm going to press one of the
现在我要按下其中一个
keyboard to zoom out to
要缩小到的键盘
100% And if you notice the way I created
100%如果你注意到我创造的方式
this these ribbons are sticking out from
这些丝带从外面伸出来
the circle a little too far from my
圆圈离我的距离太远了一点
liking so if you want to adjust this
如果你想调整这个的话
just go to your nodes tool and select
只需转到您的节点工具并选择
the object and just select these nodes
对象，然后只选择这些节点
right here let me try that
就在这里，让我试一下。
again there we go now you can use your
又来了，现在你可以用你的
left and right arrow keys to move this
向左和向右方向键来移动这个
in so I'm going to move this in one two
所以我要把这个移到一二
three and I'll come over here just for
三个人，我会来这里只是为了
the sake of symmetry you want to do the
出于对称性的考虑，你要做的是
same thing over here I'm going to select
在这里，我将选择同样的东西
these ones and move them in three steps
然后分三步移动它们
as well so one two three and I'm just
我也是一二三，我只是
pressing my arrow keys to do
按我的箭头键即可完成
that so now I will create some text to
所以现在我将创建一些文本来
place in here if you notice on this
如果你注意到这个，就放在这里
design I just placed the year in there
我刚把这一年放进去了
2023 I'll just write that I'll just
2023我只会写我只会
write the same thing in there for the
将相同的内容写在那里
sake of this tutorial obviously you
显然，为了学习本教程，您
would want to write whatever you want in
会想写任何你想写的东西
there so I'm going to write
在那里，我将写下
20 let me change the text style of that
20让我更改一下它的文本样式
let me find my original font that I was
让我找回我原来的字体
working with
使用
there we go and let me bring this in
好了，让我把这个拿进来
here like
在这里就像
that scale that down a little bit so it
把它缩小一点，这样它
fits select both we want to select both
Fits同时选择我们想要同时选择
objects there go to the alignment menu
其中的对象转到对齐菜单
and now we're going to change the
现在我们要改变
relative to last selected and then
相对于上一次选择，然后
Center that on the horizontal axis and
在水平轴上居中，
then I'll duplicate this I'll press
那我复印一下，我会按下的
command D or control D and then just
命令D或控制D然后只需
bring this over here again holding the
再把这个拿到这里来，拿着
control key while I slide this over so
Ctrl键，我把它滑过去，这样
it stays on that horizontal plane and I
它停留在那个水平面上，而我
will change this one to
将此选项更改为
23 I'll just move that over a little bit
我要把它移过去一点。
more and if you notice over here thing
更多，如果你注意到这里的东西
this part of the stroke is sticking out
划水的这一部分是突出的
a little bit as well so let me grab my
也有一点，所以让我拿起我的
nodes tool and just make a quick little
Nodes工具，只需快速创建一个
adjustment
调整，调整
there there we go and this side looks
好了，我们走了，这边看起来
good although there's a tiny bit
很好，尽管有一点
sticking out there let me select just
站在那里让我选择
that node and bring that out there we go
那个节点，然后把它带到那里，我们就去
that looks
看起来像是
better and now what we want to do is the
更好，现在我们想要做的是
design itself is is finished but if you
设计本身就是完成的，但如果你
want to color everything in and stylize
想要给每件东西上色并使其风格化
it we're going to have to make a few
如果我们要做几个
adjustments here so the first thing I
这里的调整，所以第一件事是我
want to do is select all of the items
要做的是选择所有项目
that are Strokes so I'm going to hold
这些都是中风，所以我要坚持住
shift and click on each of these Rings
按住Shift键并单击每个环
remember you got to you got to select
记住，你必须得选择
the top and the bottom half of the Ring
环的上半部分和下半部分
because those are broken up now and I
因为现在这些都被打破了，而我
want to select these pieces down here
我想在这下面选几件
and this piece over here as well I'll
还有这边的这一块，我也要
select these pieces we're basically
选择这些作品，我们基本上是
selecting everything except for the text
选择除文本之外的所有内容
items and with them all selected we want
项目并将其全部选中后，我们想要
to merge them all together or com Bine
将它们全部合并或合并
them rather we'll go to path and we will
他们宁愿我们去小路，我们会
select uh we're looking for combine
我们正在寻找联合收割机
right here and once they're combined you
就在这里，一旦他们结合在一起
can change the stroke color so let me
可以改变笔触的颜色，所以让我
come over here to my fill in stroke tab
到这里来填写我的笔划选项卡
I'll go to the stroke paint Tab and we
我将转到笔划绘制选项卡，然后我们
can make this a different color I'm
我可以把它变成不同的颜色
going to make
要做的是
this a dark shade of blue like I did in
这是一种深蓝色，就像我在
the
这个
thumbnail and now I'm going to make the
缩略图，现在我要制作
text the same color so I'm going to
用同样的颜色发短信，所以我要
select the text items I'm holding shift
选择按住Shift键的文本项
while I do this and I want to go to my
当我这么做的时候，我想去我的
dropper which is over here and I will
滴管在这里，我会
just sample a selection of this blue
只要品尝一下这种蓝色的
right there and now that's the same
就在那里和现在是一样的
color let me go to the circles and
颜色让我走进圈子，
ellipses tool and click and drag to
椭圆工具，然后单击并拖动到
create a circle and I will make this one
做一个圆圈，我就做这个
a different color I'll make this I'm
我要做一个不同的颜色，我是
going to use the colors that I used over
我要用我以前用过的颜色
here for this thumbnail I'll make this
为了这张缩略图，我会做这个
part yellow this part blue and this part
这部分是黄色，这部分是蓝色，这部分是
A light shade of red so I'll come back
浅红色，所以我会回来的
in here grab my selection tool I'll make
在这里，拿起我的选择工具，我会做
this one a lighter shade of yellow I'll
这件是浅黄色的，我要
send this to the
将此发送到
back and come back over here to my
回来，回到这里来我的
aligned distribute menu set this back to
对齐的分发菜单将此设置回
page and now I want to Center this on
佩奇，现在我想把这个放在
the page and I will just scale this up a
页面和我将把这一点放大
little bit I'm going to hold control and
有一点我要控制住自己
shift while I'm scaling that up and we
当我把它放大的时候换个位子
want this to fill in the circle but we
想把这个填满圆圈，但我们
don't want it to extend beyond the
我不希望它延伸到
circle so we want it placed within the
圆圈，因此我们希望将其放置在
boundary of that stroke there and then I
划水的边界在那里，然后我
will duplicate this I'll press control D
会复制这个，我会按下Ctrl D
to duplicate it and I'll make this one a
来复制它，我会把这个做成一个
lighter shade of blue let me just adjust
浅一点的蓝色让我调整一下
that color a little bit so we have a
这个颜色有点小，所以我们有一个
different
不同
shade and I'll lower this one down a few
遮阳板，我把这个放低几个
steps oh we don't want it that far let
哦，我们不想走那么远，让我们
me raise it one more we want it to be
我再养它一次，我们希望它成为
above the yellow one and then I'll just
在黄色的上面，然后我就
hold control and shift and scale this
按住Ctrl键、Shift键并进行缩放
down so that it's in there now and then
向下，所以它时不时地在那里
finally all we have to do now is fill in
最后，我们现在要做的就是填上
these areas so to do this I'm just going
这些区域，所以要做到这一点，我只需要
to grab my my pen tool which is located
抓起我的钢笔工具
over here or you could press B on the
在这里，或者你可以按B键
keyboard to access it and make sure you
键盘访问它，并确保您
have the correct setting here we want
这里有我们想要的正确设置
this setting right here and I'm just
就在这里，我只是
going to click to create points going
去点击创建点去
through here
穿过这里
and draw a shape that matches the shape
并绘制与该形状匹配的形状
of this object here and let me make that
这个物体，让我来做这个
a lighter shade of red like that I'm
像这样浅一点的红色，我是
going to remove The Stroke by holding
用按住的方法来消除中风
shift and clicking the X grab the
按住Shift键并单击X，然后将
selection tool and I will lower this a
选择工具和我将降低这一点
few steps until it's beneath everything
再走几步，它就会消失在一切之下
there we go looking good and now I'm
我们看起来很好，现在我
just going to instead of drawing another
只是去画而不是画另一幅
shape over here I'm just going to
在这里塑造我要做的是
duplicate this and flip it so I'll press
复制这个并翻转它，这样我就可以按
controll D I will flip it on the
控制器D I会将其翻转到
horizontal axis and then just bring this
水平轴，然后把这个
over here and I will lower this down as
在这里，我会把这个放下来
well and now at this point you can you
现在，在这一点上你可以
can import your own graphic or your own
可以导入您自己的图形或您自己的图形
icon or whatever you want to put in
图标或任何你想放进去的东西
there uh for this this demonstration I
这个，呃，这个演示我
just used the inkscape logo I'm not
刚用了Inkscape的标志我不是
going to go through that and do that
我要经历那件事，做那件事
again it's already there but you get the
再说一次，它已经在那里了，但你得到了
idea you can now put whatever you want
现在你可以把任何你想要的东西
in there and once you're finished uh and
在那里，一旦你完成了，呃，
you're happy with everything you can
你对你所能做的一切都很满意
either save this design as it is right
要么按原样保存此设计
now or you can select the text if you
现在，或者您可以选择文本，如果您
select the text and go to path object to
选择文本并转到路径对象以
path you can now edit the design so let
路径您现在可以编辑设计，以便让
me go and convert this to object to path
我去把它转换成对象到路径
and now I can select everything and I
现在我可以选择一切，我
can move it around and resize it if I
我可以移动它并调整大小，如果我
want if you try moving moving it around
如果你试着动一动它就会想要
and resizing it before converting that
并在转换之前调整它的大小
text to a path then you're going to lose
将文本发送到路径，则您将丢失
the text on the path it's not going to
路径上的文本不会
be wrapped around that Circle anymore uh
再绕着那个圆圈走了，嗯
but the downside is is once you do that
但缺点是一旦你这么做了
now you can't edit the text anymore so
现在您不能再编辑文本，因此
make sure you don't do that until you're
确保你不会这样做，直到你
completely happy with how the text looks
对文本的外观非常满意
and let's say for example you want to
比方说，你想要
scale this up a little bit I'm going to
把这个放大一点，我要
hold control I'm going to scale this up
控制住，我要把它放大
it's going to make those Strokes look a
它会让这些中风看起来像是
little
一点儿
smaller because the weight of them is
更小，因为它们的重量是
fixed relative to the size and once
相对于大小和一次固定
you're happy with that as well you can
你对此也很满意，你可以
turn this setting back on that says uh
将此设置重新打开，显示为嗯
scaling objects scale the stroke width
缩放对象缩放笔触宽度
by the same proportion and I'll just
以同样的比例，我只会
group everything together I will go to
把所有东西放在一起，我会去的
object and select group and there you go
对象并选择GROUP，就可以了
now you can scale this and edit it
现在您可以对其进行缩放和编辑
however you want now you have a simple
无论您想要什么，现在您有一个简单的
logo that you can work with so that's
您可以使用的徽标，因此
how you can go about creating that logo
如何着手创建该徽标
with inkscape if you have any questions
如果您有任何问题，请使用Inkscape
let me know and as always thanks for
让我知道，并一如既往地感谢
watching if you found this lesson useful
看看你是否觉得这一课有用
then consider checking out my inkscape
那就考虑看看我的Inkscape吧
master class it's a collection of over
大师类，它是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我浏览了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示它们
how they work kind of like how I did in
它们的工作原理有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人的
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提出问题的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
只要你愿意，随时向我寻求帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最棒的是没有月刊
members ship fees you just pay $17 one
会员运费你只需付17美元一张
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间和你在一起的生活我将拥有
some information about that down below
下面是关于这一点的一些信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地查看
thanks for
感谢
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
观看